# Gulchohra Umarli - Front End developer

gulchohra.umarli@gmail.com | +994 70 258 44 74 Baku, Azerbaijan | LinkedIn

## **Summary:**

I, Gulchohra Umarli, have been working as an Angular Front-end developer for 2 years. I am a quick learner, always open to development.

During my work experience, I have been involved in writing the user interface of many projects such as logistics, cargo transportation, etc., supporting other projects written from the beginning, etc.

### **Work Experience:**

### Middle Front End developer, "Uniser Group" MMC

May 2024 - Present

- User-friendly, adaptive and responsive websites with optimized cross-browser compatibility and runtime performance.
- Optimize website performance by minimizing load times and reducing page weight.

### Front End developer, "Uniser Group" MMC

Sep 2022 - May 2024

- Debug seamless web applications on multiple browsers and platforms.
- Managed code repositories, review tools, and continuous integration processes to improve website analytics and end user feedback.

### Intern Front End developer, "Uniser Group" MMC

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

- I improved my abilities about web development, how we can work with team and get more skills.
- Support ready project and to make some changes in their UI and integrate them with database.

## **Intern Front End developer**, Algorithmics Azerbaijan Feb 2022 - Jun 2022

- I learned how we can work with front-end languages, tools, libraries to make more efficient, reliable, safe etc. products and so on.
- Developed user interface components and implemented them following well-known React.js workflows.

## **Education:**

# **Bacholors of Computer Engineering,**

Azerbaijan State University of Oil and Industry.

## **Skills:**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind
- Angular
- React
- Mateial UI
- RESTful api
- RxJS
- Context API
- Redux
- jQuery(base)
- Git & GitHub

# Languages:

- Azerbaijan [ Native ]
- English [ Intermediate B1 ]
- Turkish [ Advanced C1 ]